Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2015
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2015
Mus. Arc. 74
Haupt, Irene
7 CD-ROMs (375 digital images in tiff format)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains 375 digital images of musicians who participated in the June in Buffalo 2015 at the University at Buffalo and the associated June in Buffalo Performance Institute, including guest composers Roger Reynolds, Martin Bresnick, Brian Ferneyhough, August Read Thomas, Harvey Sollberger, Charles Wuorinen, and Steven Stucky.
All files in the collection were renamed to reflect chronological sequence. Original filenames stated in the container list are transcribed as stated on the CDs as received. Renamed files are stored in the Institutional Repository.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2015.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The entire collection of images from June in Buffalo 2015 is available in University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2015 contains 375 digital images of participants in the festival for 2015. The list of musicians includes guest composers Roger Reynolds, Martin Bresnick, Brian Ferneyhough, August Read Thomas, Harvey Sollberger, Charles Wuorinen, and Steven Stucky. Performers include Irvine Arditti, Brad Lubman, Julia Bentley, Eric Huebner, Tom Kolor, Heather Buck, Ethan Herschenfeld, and Yuki Numata Resnick. Ensembles include the New York New Music Ensemble, Meridian Arts Ensemble, the Slee Sinfonietta, Talujon Percussion ensemble, and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra.
Arrangement
One series arranged chiefly chronologically.
Container List
- Nicholas Emmanuel, Cynthia Bryndis Schilling, Anna Whistler, Benjamin Havey, and Hangyu Bai rehearsing Morton Feldman's Five pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Feldman Five Pianos.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_001.tif)
- Anna Whistler, Benjamin Havey, and Hangyu Bai rehearsing Morton Feldman's Five pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Performance Institute concert Feldman Five pianos.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_002.tif)
- Eric Huebner, Benjamin Herrington, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Charles Wuorinen's Trombone trio at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Eric Huebner piano Benjamin Herrington Trombone, Tom Kolor percussion.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_003.tif)
- Eric Huebner, Benjamin Herrington, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Charles Wuorinen's Trombone trio at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Charles Wuorinen Trombone Trio Benjamin Herrington Trombone Eric huebner piano, Tom Kolor percussion.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_004.tif)
- Eric Huebner, Benjamin Herrington, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Charles Wuorinen's Trombone trio at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Eric Huebner piano, Tom Kolor percussion, Benjamin Herrington Trombone.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_005.tif)
- Eric Huebner, Benjamin Herrington, and Tom Kolor rehearsing Charles Wuorinen's Trombone trio at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Eric Huebner pianioo, Benjamin Herrington Trombone, Tom Kolor percussion.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_006.tif)
- Pianists Nicholas Emmanuel, Benjamin Havey, Anna Whistler, Cynthia Bryndis Schilling, and Hangyu Bai at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Performance Institute concert.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_007.tif)
- Trumpeter Samuel Wells at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Benjamin Havey, piano.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_008.tif)
- Trumpeter Samuel Wells at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Benjamin Havey piano.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_009.tif)
- Clarinetist Pei-Lun Tsai performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's Der kleine Harlekin at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Stockhausen Der Kleine Harlekin.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_010.tif)
- Clarinetist Pei-Lun Tsai performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's Der kleine Harlekin at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Pei-Lun Tsai claninet Baird Hall Saturday May 30 Performance Institute Concert.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_011.tif)
- Clarinetist Pei-Lun Tsai performing Karlheinz Stockhausen's Der kleine Harlekin at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Pei-Lun Tsai clarinet Karlheinz Stockhausen Der Kleine Harlekin (1977).tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_012.tif)
- Marimba player Max Fahland performing Alejandro Viñao's Burritt variations at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Burritt Variations (2012) by Alejandro Vinao- Max Fahland marimba.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_013.tif)
- Violinist Yuki Numata Resnick and composer Andrew Greenwald at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Yuki Numata Resnick, violin and composer Andrew Greenwald world premiere.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_014.tif)
- Violinist Yuki Numata Resnick and composer Andrew Greenwald at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-30, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Yuki Numata Resnick, violin world premiere by Andrew Greenwald.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_015.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Ian Antonio, Tom Kolor, Michael Lipsey, and Matthew Gold rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0173.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_016.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Ian Antonio, Tom Kolor, Michael Lipsey, and Matthew Gold rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0176.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_017.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Ian Antonio, Tom Kolor, Michael Lipsey, and Matthew Gold rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0182.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_018.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman with June in Buffalo 2015 Performance Institute participants, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name PERCUSSION dANIEL dRUCKMAN pERFORMANCE iNSTITUTE.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_019.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman with June in Buffalo 2015 Performance Institute participants, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0185.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_020.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman with June in Buffalo Performance Institute 2015 participant Joe Desotelle, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0187.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_021.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman with June in Buffalo Performance Institute 2015 participant Joe Desotelle, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name PERCUSSION dANIEL dRUCKMAN.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_022.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting a rehearsal of the New York New Music Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0192.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_023.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting a rehearsal of the New York New Music Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0194.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_024.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting a rehearsal of the New York New Music Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0195.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_025.tif)
- Cover of score for Harvey Sollberger's Advancing moment, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0198.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_026.tif)
- Cover of score to Lukas Foss's Echoi, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Mia Detwilwe violin, Yuki Numata Resnick viola, JonathaN gOLOVE CELLO, eRIC hUEBNER PIANO.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_027.tif)
- Violinist Mia Detwiler, pianist Eric Huebner, cellist Jonathan Golove, and violist Yuki Numata Resnick rehearsing Steven Stucky's Piano quartet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name eRIC hUEBNER PIANO jONATHAN gOLOVE CELLO yUKI nUMATA rESNICK VIOLA mIA dETWILER VIOLIN.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_028.tif)
- Violinist Mia Detwiler, pianist Eric Huebner, cellist Jonathan Golove, and violist Yuki Numata Resnick rehearsing Steven Stucky's Piano quartet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name eRIC hUEBNER PIANO, jONATHAN gOLOVE CELLO, yUKI nUMATA rESNICK VIOLA, mIA dETWILER VIOLIN.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_029.tif)
- Meridian Arts Ensemble rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0203.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_030.tif)
- Composer Elliott Grabill at a rehearsal with the Meridian Arts Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0205.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_031.tif)
- Composer Elliott Grabill at rehearsal of his work Rust belt by the Meridian Arts Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0206.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_032.tif)
- Composer Elliott Grabill at rehearsal of his work Rust belt by the Meridian Arts Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0207.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_033.tif)
- Composer Elliott Grabill at rehearsal of his work Rust belt by the Meridian Arts Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0208.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_034.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman and composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0211.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_035.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman and composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0213.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_036.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman and composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 black and white digital image (tiff format); Original file name dANIEL dRUCKMAN mARTIN bRESNICK.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_037.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman and composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name dANIEL dRUCKMAN PERCUSSION mARTIN bRESNICK COMPOSER-.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_038.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman and composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Martin Bresnick Fruckman.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_039.tif)
- Composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 black and white digital image (tiff format); Original file name Martin Bresnick composer.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_040.tif)
- Composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 black and white digital image (tiff format); Original file name Martin Bresnick.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_041.tif)
- Composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name COMPOSER mARTIN bRESNICK June IN bUFFALO 2015.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_042.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro and composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0223.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_043.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber and pianist Stephen Gosling with composer Martin Bresnick rehearsing Bresnick's Bird as prophet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0225.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_044.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber and pianist Stephen Gosling with composer Martin Bresnick rehearsing Bresnick's Bird as prophet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name cURTIS mACOMBER mARTIN bRESNICK sTEPHEN gOSLING PIANO.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_045.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber and pianist Stephen Gosling with composer Martin Bresnick rehearsing Bresnick's Bird as prophet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name cURTIS mACOMBER mARTIN bRESNICK sTEPHEN gOSLING, PIANO.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_046.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro and composer Martin Bresnick at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0226.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_047.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name VIOLIN cURTIS mACOMBER.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_048.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0228.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_049.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name cURTIS mACOMBER VIOLIN.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_050.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name cURTIS mACOMBER, VIOLIN.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_051.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber and pianist Stephen Gosling with composer Martin Bresnick rehearsing Bresnick's Bird as prophet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name COMPOSER mARTIN bRESNICK cURTIS mACOMBER VIOLIN sTEPHEN gOSLING PIANO.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_052.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber and pianist Stephen Gosling rehearsing Martin Bresnick's Bird as prophet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0231.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_053.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber and pianist Stephen Gosling with composer Martin Bresnick rehearsing Bresnick's Bird as prophet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0233.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_054.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber with composer Martin Bresnick rehearsing Bresnick's Bird as prophet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name mARTIN bRESNICK COMPOSER cURTIS mACOMBER VIOLIN.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_055.tif)
- Violinist Curtis Macomber and pianist Stephen Gosling with composer Martin Bresnick rehearsing Bresnick's Bird as prophet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name COMPOSER mARTIN bRESNICK cURTIS mACOMBER, VIOLIN.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_056.tif)
- Clarinet with microphone attached to its bell, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0236.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_057.tif)
- Composer Martin Bresnick with New York New Music Ensemble members Curtis Macomber, Jean Kopperud, Stephen Gosling, and Chris Finckel at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0238.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_058.tif)
- Title page of score to Lukas Foss's Echoi, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0241.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_059.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name dANIEL dRUCKMAN PERCUSSION.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_060.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name dANIEL dRUCKMAN.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_061.tif)
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0245.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_062.tif)